A Guide to the Joshua Lederberg personal papers, Subject File FA1087
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File, 1
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Ad Hoc Committee on Residential Facilities, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 25-28)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Retirement (Box 54, Folder 29-33)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Revson Foundation (Box 54, Folder 33A)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Rubenstein (Box 54, Folder 33B)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Safety and Code Compliance (Box 54, Folder 34-36)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Senior Admin. Staff Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 37-42)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Smoking Legislation (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Sponsored Programs (Box 54, Folder 44-45)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Summer College Program, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Telephone System, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Telecommunications, 1990 April-May (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Tenex Executive Manual, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Travel (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Committee on Trust and Estate Gift Plans (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Weizmann Institute of Science - Meeting, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Women's Association (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Faculty Search Committee Form Letter (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Women - CG Meeting, 1989 December 8 (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Miscellaneous, 1990 May (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - International Technology Transfer Study - October 28, 1986 - First Draft, 1986 October 28 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - International Technology Transfer Study - October 28, 1986 - Second Draft, 1986 October 28 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - International Technology Transfer Study - Sixth Draft - Pre-COSEPUP Review (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Retirement, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reviews (of Biophysics) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Alister Brass - April 24, 1981 - May 2, 1988 Annual Reviews (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. Board, 1981 May 2 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Joshua Lederberg - Annual Reviews Board, 1980 April 23 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reviews Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 55, Folder 9-10)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Business Affairs, 1981 April 24 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors - Business Affairs Committee (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Editorial Affairs (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Annual Review of Public Health (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Annual Review History (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Stationary (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc., 1980 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Annual Review of Nutrition, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Annual Review of Genetics (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Board Committee, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Editor Affairs, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Search Committee, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Annual Review of Science, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - Public Health, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Annual Reviews (Kaufman), 1974 May (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc., 1967-1971 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc. - J. M. Luck Prize (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reviews, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1979-1984 (Box 55, Folder 30-33)
  - Clean Sites Inc. - Meetings, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 34-35)
  - Clean Sites Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
  - The Camille and Henry Dreyfus Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 56, Folder 7-35)
  - The Camille and Henry Dreyfus Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 1-11)
  - NIH Recombinant DNA Research (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Laboratory Safety Monograph - A Supplement to the NIH Guidelines for Recombinant DNA Research, 1978 July (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Recombinant DNA Volume 4 - Volume 7, 1978-1982 (Box 57, Folder 14-19)
  - NASA "The Saturn System", 1978 February 9-11 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - NASA "Space Missions to Comets", 1977 October (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - NASA "Exterrestrial Life: A Bibliography Part I", 1964 September (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Viking Mars Expedition, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Publications of the Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL), 1976 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - NASA - "Mars as Viewed by Mariner 9", 1974 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - NASA - "Asteroids" An Exploration Assessment", 1978 January 19-21 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - NASA - "Pioneer Odyssey Encounter with a Gaint", 1975 February 24 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Quest - Autumn 1977 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - NASA - A First Comet Mission: Report of the Comet Halley Science Working Group - Executive Summary, 1977 July (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - NASA - A First Comet Mission: Report of the Comet Halley Science Working Group", 1977 July (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Viking Lander System - Primary Mission Performance Report, 1977 April (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - NASA - Viking Lander Imaging Investigation - Picture Catalog of Primary Mission Experiment Data Record - Robert B. Tucker, 1978 February (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Review of Scientific Instruments - F. S. Brown, 1978 February (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Science, 1978 October (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - NASA - Results of Analyses Performed on Soil Adjacent to Penetrators Emplaced into Sediments at McCook, Nebraska January 1976 - M. Blanchard, 1977 May (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Astronautics and Aeronautics, Mars Worth Another Look, 1976 November (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Science, 1976 August 27 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - NASA - A Mars 1984 Mission: Report of the Mars Science Working Group, 1977 July (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - NASA - FY 1976 Progress Report of a Feasibility Study Evaluating the Use of Surface Penetrators for Planetary Exploration - M. Blanchard, 1976 November (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - TRW - Mars Viking, 1976 August (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - NAS - Life Sciences in Space (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Viking '76 and Mars: The Search Begins (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - NASA - Report of a Study by the Mars Science Advisory Committee to the Planetary Programs Office, 1973 November (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1964 - Project Report: Television Experiment Part I: Investigators' Reports Mariner IV Pictures at Mars - Robert B. Leighton, 1967 December (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1971 Project Final Report Volume II: Preliminary Science Results, 1972 February 1 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - EOS, 1976 October (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - NASA - "Mariner Mars Final Project Report Volume III - J. A. Stalkanp, 1971 September 15 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1969: A Preliminary Report (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Journal of Geophysical Research - One Year's Processing and Interpretation: An Overview, 1971 January 10 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - NASA - BIOSPEX: Bio Space Experiments - A Compendium of Life Sciences Experiments Carried on US Spacecraft - Michele Anderson, 1979 June (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - CIT - Bibliography of Viking Mars Science, First Edition, 1978 May 19 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - NASA - Announcement of Opportunity, 1978 June 29 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Publications of the Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) 1977, 1978 May 1 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - NASA - Mars Surface Penetrator - System Description - Edited by Larry A. Manning, 1977 June (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - NASA - Summer Workshop on Near Earth Resources, 1977 August 6-13 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - NASA - Tracking and Data System Support for the Viking 1975 Mission to Mars, Volume I: Pre-Launch Planning, Implementation, and Testing, 1977 January (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - NASA - Tracking and Data System Support for the Viking 1975 Mission to Mars, Volume III: Planetary Operations, 1977 September 1 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Mars: The Viking Discoveries, 1977 October (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Space Shuttle, 1975 February (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1971 Television Picture Catalog: Experiment Design and Picture Data - Dennis Crosby, 1977 August (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Astronautics and Aeronautics, Volume I, Addendum I - Viking on Mars, 1969 November (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1971 Project Final Report Volume VI, 1973 July (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Martin Marietta - The Viking Mission to Mars, 1975 August 12 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Viking Project Bulletin, 1976 December (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Michael, Don - Proposed Studies on the Implications of Peaceful Space Activities for Human Affairs, 1962 March (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1964 - Final Project Report, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Report to the Congress - More Emphasis Needed on Data Analysis Phase of Space Science Programs, 1977 June (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1971 Mars Orbiter Missions (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Control Networks for the Galilean Satellites, 1979 November (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - NAS-NRC - Biology and Exploration of Mars: Summary and Conclusions of a Study by the Space Science Board (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - The Viking Lander Biology Instrument, 1975 August (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - NASA - On the Habitability of Mars, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Lawrence B. Hall, editor, Planetary Quarantine, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - NASA - The Viking Mosaic Catalog, Volume I and II, 1962 March (Box 59, Folder 17-18)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Annual Report, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - 1982 Annual Program Plan, 1981 October 28 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Health Sciences, 1981 June 25 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Program Plan, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1978 July 19 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Proceedings of the First Annual Meeting, 1981 November 17-18 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1982 January 20 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1982 May 19 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1982 November 18 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Council, 1980 May 28 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Report of a Study Strengthening US Programs to Improve Health in Developing Countries, 1978 April (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Report of a Study of Manpower for Primary Health Care, 1978 May (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Draft Report - Marijuana and Health, 1981 November (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1978 September 27 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1979 September 12 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1980 May 28 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1978 March 22 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1978 January 18 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1977 December 14 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Workshop, 1980 September 5 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Search Committee, 1979 August 14 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1981 March 18 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1981 March 19 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Minutes of the Council Calendar Year 1977 and December 19, 1973, 1973, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1978 May 17 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1978 November 8 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Membership, 1981 October 29 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Conference on the Federal Research and Development Budget for 1982, 1981 October 26-27 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1981 September 16 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Nominations for Council Terms 1981-1983 - Action Items (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Revson Conference on Technology Assessment and Diffusion (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1981 January 15 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1981 June 2 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Meeting of the Council, 1981 July 16-17 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Planning Study for an Ongoing Study of Costs of Environmental Related Health Effects Committee Meeting, 1980 October 20 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Negative, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Completed Applications, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications and Inquiries, 1960-1966 (Box 61, Folder 4-8)
  - Recommendations and Promotions (Box 61)
  - Audit Committee - Financial Statements - Laboratory Budgets (Box 61)
  - Bionet Adv. Committee Meeting, 1984 May 4 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Bionet, 1986 May 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Bionet (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Aging Research (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Commission on Science, Law and the Food Supply, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
- Maps and Flat Files, 2
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Chryse Region of Mars, Map I-939, 1975 (Box 47)
    Retrieval times for maps and flat files may exceed 24 hours. Individual items may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Cydonia Region of Mars, Map I-946, 1975 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Acardia Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-963, 1975 (Box 47)
  - NASA Photographs (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the OXIA Palus Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-955, 1975 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Geological Map of the Oxia Palus Quadrangle of Mars - Don E. Wilhelm, Map I-895, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Area Relief Map of the Aeolis Quadrangle of Mars - David H. Scott and John W. Allingham, Map I-935, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Aeolis Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-1000, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Aeolis Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-1001, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Chryse Region of Mars, Map I-983, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of Oxia Palus Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-978, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of Oxia Palus Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-978, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Lunae Palus Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-971, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Mare Acidalum Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-979, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Magaritifer Sinus Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-975, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Geologic Map of the Hellas Quadrangle of Mars - Donald B. Potter, Map I-941, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Mare Australe Area of Mars, Map I-970, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Diacria Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-989, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Erythraseum Region of Mars, Map I-986, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Coprates Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-976, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Mare Boreum Area of Mars, Map I-969, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Topographic Map of the Phoenicis Lacus Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-984, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of the Mare Acidalium Quadrangle of Mars, Map I-958, 1975 (Box 47)
  - Viking - Shaded Relief Map of Mars, Map I-940, 1975 (Box 47)
  - Viking - High Resolution Mariner 9 Pictures in the Chryse Region of Mars, Map I-991, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Viking - High Resolution Mariner 9 Pictures in the Cydonia Region of Mars, Map I-988, 1976 (Box 47)